bigscreen.com 2018-01-26

# Privacy Policy - The BigScreen Cinema Guide

## Privacy Policy

> This document explains what information we collect from you, why we collect it, and what we will and will not do with it. It also explains certain issues involved with advertising that appears on our site, and how that relates to privacy concerns that you may have. Please note: We reserve the right to change the policies documented here without notice.

Last Updated: November 15, 2017

## What Information We Collect When You Customize The BigScreen Cinema Guide

In order to provide you with a customized experience, we ask you for the following items of information:

  * Your Name
  * Your E-Mail Address
  * A Password of Your Choice
  * Your ZIP Code

## How We Collect That Information (Cookies)

We use a technology available in every current browser, called _Cookies_. When we ask for your information, we store it in our records, and assign you a unique ID. This ID is stored on your browser using a cookie, so that when you return to The BigScreen Cinema Guide, we can retrieve your settings and use them to customize your visit with us. The only information that is stored in your browser is the ID code, and that cookie is only accessible by this site. If you would like to read more about cookies, and what they can and cannot do, check out the [Wikipedia entry for HTTP cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Browser_cookie).

If you have chosen only to provide us with your ZIP code, instead of customizing The BigScreen Cinema Guide, we do store that ZIP code in what's called a temporary cookie. This temporary cookie is deleted by your browser when you exit the program, and is not stored like the ID mentioned in the previous example. The next time you run your browser and visit this site, you will be asked for your ZIP code again.

We also utilize third party advertising solutions, which use cookies to determine which ad to display, if applicable. The ads that you are shown are not tied in any way to your custom account information.

## Why We Collect That Information and What We Do With It

We ask for your name so that we can welcome you by name when you return to the site. If you submit a Reader Review, a comment to a Journal article or about a movie theater, your name is used to identify you on your submission. Take a look at our Reader Reviews, Journal, and Theater Comments for examples of how we do this.

Your E-Mail address is needed so that we can contact you if we need to. If you forget your password when logging into the site from another computer, we give you the option of having your password E-Mailed to the address you gave us. If we have questions about a review you submitted, we will contact you at that address so that we can post your review as soon as possible. We will not publish your E-Mail address anywhere on the site.

To keep others from accessing your custom settings, your settings are protected with a password that you choose. You only need to login to access your custom settings once, as we store a cookie on your browser that connects your browser to your settings.

Probably the most important piece of information that we can get from you is your ZIP code. We use your ZIP code to determine which theaters are closest to your location, so that you can select nearby theaters easily.

## What We Will Not Do With Your Information

We will not willingly share your personal information with any third party. We believe that your personal information is yours to share with us, and no one else needs to have access to it. We will not willingly or knowingly sell, trade, or otherwise share the information you provide to us with anyone not directly associated with The BigScreen Cinema Guide, unless required to do so by law.

## A Special Note About the Third Party Advertising on Our Site

We use Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of a browser cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit here and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

In order to provide access to this web site for free, we have to display advertising to offset our costs. This is a fact of life and is part of the agreement you make when you visit web sites without paying for access. You can control some third party vendors' use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting the [Digital Advertising Alliance's WebChoices tool](http://optout.aboutads.info/), where you can see which advertising systems are delivering customized ads, and choose how you want your browser to be tracked.

If you don't like the idea of advertising and that advertisers might be gathering information about your browsing, we recommend signing up for our VIP Service, which blocks all the third-party advertising on our site. It makes using the site a lot better without the ads, and we also provide you with extra features as a way of saying thank-you for supporting us directly! We would much prefer to have all our readers be VIP's, because it would allow us to focus completely on delivering the best content we possibly can, without having to be concerned about placing ads on our pages to pay the bills. We do understand, however, that not everyone would like to become a VIP Member, so that's why we offer the choice!

### Related Web Sites

### Use of Google Analytics

This site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. This analytical tool uses cookies and other technologies to help analyze how our readers use this site. In order to create reports and provide us with usage information, data including site usage, including visitor IP address, is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' use of the website, compile statistical reports on site activity, and other services relating to site activity and internet usage. Google offers the ability to opt out from tracking through Google Analytics cookies; for more information, visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.
